<resources>

    <string name="lorem_medium">
         Powder wafer brownie tiramisu bear claw dragée tootsie roll. Chocolate bar marzipan donut sugar plum
        toffee gingerbread chupa chups cookie. Apple pie marzipan chocolate cake powder gingerbread jelly-o
        gummi bears. Toffee soufflé caramels bonbon halvah fruitcake carrot cake tootsie roll dragée. Cupcake
        tiramisu bear claw lollipop bear claw. Cheesecake biscuit sugar plum sugar plum powder icing powder
        croissant biscuit. Lemon drops chupa chups bonbon. Gummi bears biscuit toffee carrot cake. Candy muffin
        macaroon gingerbread caramels.
        Fruitcake topping sweet roll sweet roll cupcake fruitcake bonbon chupa chups. Biscuit cake halvah pie. Jujubes
        candy cookie liquorice carrot cake sugar plum jelly beans. Carrot cake chocolate cake topping ice cream.
        Wafer gingerbread chocolate ice cream oat cake dessert jelly beans. Topping gummi bears chupa chups chupa
        chups.
        Powder cotton candy muffin gingerbread. Biscuit marzipan apple pie macaroon cheesecake. Oat cake cake brownie
        cookie
        liquorice toffee. Pastry sesame snaps cake ice cream pie bear claw jelly. Chocolate biscuit cotton candy
        ice cream. Cupcake candy toffee jelly-o brownie.
        Lollipop cheesecake fruitcake chupa chups. Bonbon sugar plum tootsie roll chocolate sugar plum apple pie
        topping.
        Chocolate cake gingerbread biscuit brownie powder danish cupcake gingerbread gummi bears. Jelly tootsie
        roll powder. Biscuit cookie apple pie gingerbread. Gummi bears biscuit croissant.
        Oat cake topping gingerbread marzipan chupa chups carrot cake. Lollipop dessert marshmallow lollipop jelly beans
        dessert chupa chups chupa chups macaroon. Sugar plum muffin apple pie cookie chocolate sweet roll donut wafer.
        Ice cream powder jelly beans apple pie fruitcake jelly macaroon. Dessert lollipop pie powder wafer toffee.
        Sesame snaps pie brownie croissant. Carrot cake tiramisu sesame snaps apple pie halvah. Pudding gingerbread
        marzipan toffee oat cake.
        Ice cream soufflé oat cake ice cream caramels. Toffee cake carrot cake candy canes pastry marshmallow gummies.
        Chocolate bar icing sweet roll tart chocolate cake pudding tootsie roll. Cheesecake cotton candy dessert
        tart candy canes croissant pie. Wafer lemon drops oat cake bonbon gingerbread. Carrot cake gingerbread
        jujubes icing halvah. Dragée cookie sweet roll jelly-o sugar plum soufflé pie cake. Sugar plum pastry jelly-o
        soufflé jujubes. Cotton candy lollipop cotton candy pie sweet roll powder donut apple pie.
        Carrot cake chocolate powder bear claw. Croissant muffin muffin. Marzipan lemon drops gummi bears. Jelly-o
        liquorice halvah. Sweet caramels fruitcake pudding cotton candy candy canes tiramisu muffin. Tootsie roll
        cake jelly beans tootsie roll tiramisu cake jelly-o pastry fruitcake. Pudding tootsie roll toffee marshmallow
        tart candy canes. Muffin candy canes brownie caramels. Brownie bear claw muffin gingerbread pie pie.
        Croissant cupcake lemon drops cake sweet roll tart cotton candy ice cream tart. Pastry danish apple pie sweet
        roll biscuit powder sugar plum jelly halvah. Toffee bonbon lemon drops donut gummies sweet lollipop toffee
        gummies. Macaroon pastry jelly-o ice cream jujubes liquorice marshmallow danish. Lollipop chocolate bar
        chocolate cake croissant apple pie cupcake jelly-o icing jelly beans. Jujubes tootsie roll biscuit cotton
        candy. Sweet jelly-o marzipan tootsie roll sweet roll muffin. Fruitcake pudding biscuit halvah muffin
        chocolate dessert tiramisu jelly beans. Liquorice gummies soufflé chocolate jujubes. Powder cupcake
        croissant bonbon topping marzipan.
        Cake fruitcake icing gummi bears. Gummies cake tart fruitcake brownie pastry. Carrot cake pie liquorice soufflé
        topping candy canes carrot cake jelly beans. Icing dragée bonbon caramels ice cream powder gummi bears
        cookie. Jelly-o tart apple pie halvah jelly lollipop halvah chocolate bar dragée. Sweet roll icing cupcake
        dragée jelly-o carrot cake donut croissant tart. Carrot cake liquorice carrot cake cookie croissant lemon
        drops dragée dragée jelly. Jelly jelly beans croissant ice cream pastry oat cake sugar plum gingerbread.
        Sweet liquorice cake. Bonbon muffin oat cake icing caramels. Toffee marshmallow dragée gummi bears jelly sweet.
        Gummies marzipan bear claw donut dragée chocolate bar. Pastry cookie apple pie. Danish apple pie gummies
        lemon drops cheesecake candy canes pastry tart soufflé. Cotton candy cheesecake muffin candy topping tart
        chupa chups gummi bears. Pie sweet cotton candy bonbon biscuit jelly-o tootsie roll pie sweet roll. Carrot
        cake cake danish. Liquorice wafer jelly beans marzipan bear claw toffee soufflé tootsie roll.
    </string>


</resources>
